Hello, I'm Rena Miyashita.
Today my teacher will whisper in your ear and tickle you a lot
So please feel good and show me your face
She whispers gently like this
I recommend you to wear earphones or headphones when you go out.
You'll feel much better!
Hello, my name is Lena Miyashita and this is a home-study class
Nice meeting you
Where are your parents?
Oh really
Is it okay if they come in without permission
Oh, is that so?
Then I'll interrupt you.
How's it going to be okay
Hmm ... in this case
Because the bottom of the song is a related noun
If you translate
The song his father loved was Pops
It will become an old pops
It was a problem.
So, based on what you've learned so far
try to solve this problem
Yeah yeah
This question is kind of difficult
so do your best
My mom asked me
and my friend'son
told him
that I should teach him
but will he be able
if i teach like this?
Is it okay for you
Thank You
Then, solve the problem as it is.
What? Where have you been looking at since a while ago ?
I've noticed from the beginning
You were watching my erotic place all the time
After all ,I'm interested in that kind of thing
Do you always think about erotic things and peep
What are you doing?
Then, show me how you usually do it.
What's the matter with you
Aren't embarrassed
I'll look at it
Hurry up and show your penis
It is cute to be embarrassed
Great
You have a penis like this
Hey, hurry up and pet the baby.
I'll look at you when you're petting a lot of things
Petting face
It's cute
Does it feel good?
Hey hey
Can i touch just for awhile
Something has grown
Do you want me to help
Do you want me to help you?
I'll help you, so don't do it yourself.
How is it? Does your skin feel good and slimy ?
Your face has become harder than before
Then let's make your skin more moist
Is the moisture in the pores comfortable for you
It feels good
I'm happy when you look comfortable.
Be more stiff?
What's wrong, are you going to go already ?
You said be patient
If you endure it will feel much better
Hmm what
Do i look like your panties
You don't like it?
Well, you're so naughty.
I can not help it...
Is this okay with you now ?
Then let me scrub your body again
Your body is harder than before
After all ,I wanted to see your panties
Do you feel good
Oh! It's gone
Did that make yourself feel good
Did you feel better?
I haven't said that it's okay yet.
But, he is still very healthy!
Let me give you a little more massage
How do you like this kind of thing
Does it feel good
Then what about this
This feels good too
So how about this
Great
Wow, it's hard again.
Then what about this?
You have a sexy face again
Did you want to put out your teeth again by any chance
Well
I'll count ten so if it becomes zero
It is okay
So be patient until then
Here we go
Ten
Halfway there.
You're almost there?
Just a little more, so hang in there!
One, two...
Great.
You were able to bear it properly
Did you feel good?
But I gave you twice and still so hard
Because we could endure
A little more
As a reward
I'll lick
Don'tell your mother.
How do you feel?
Your chinchin is very warm
It's getting puffy again
Does it feel so good
Do you like the teacher
So how about this
It's the third time, but you're out again like this
Did it feel good?
Well then
Let me make you feel better
Shall we go to bed
Because it is absolutely a secret
Chuu feels good
Then I'll do something more pleasant for you.
Do you like your nipples?
You're very nervous, aren't you
Would like me to lick your nipples too
Okay
Let's lick a lot
Wow
It really looks good
I'making it a secret.
You love your nipples, don't you?
Make sure you keep it from your mother!
Let's make her feel good
Your stomach is hard again
It got this big again
Then let me stroke while licking the nappies
I'll lick you a lot.
What's wrong?
You want me to lick your chin, don't you ?
All right!
Let' s do it
Do you feel good in my mouth
No way
Did not expect that
Are we going again
no
No, I want to feel good too.
Hold on a little longer
You were going to say it again
no
Then make sensei feel better
How is the teacher's underwear?
cute
Good
So touch your body
Touch my neck.
Be gentle, okay?
It feels good!
Touch my neck too
Do you like your teacher's boobs ?
Do you like my boobs?
Touch my nipples.
Don'tell anyone, okay
It feels so good
Hey, can you touch my tongue?
If I touch your tongue like that...
...you'll feel better.
Hey, touch me directly.
It's embarrassing to look at you like that...
Hey, rub my belly too.
Is the teacher's manko warm?
Rub it more...
Ouch!
You're good at touching me.
Can I lick you again?
Are you ready?
Hey, do you want to put this silver towel in the teacher's room.
I've wanted this since we first met
Please keep it a secret
It is only between two of us
It's a secret.
It feels so hard...
But it feels good because it is big and hard
Your tits feel really good
Sensei, my back won't stop
Hey, can I move a lot?
Look at the place where you are in.
It feels so good!
Make it harder
Ah, it'so hot.
It feels good!
Which one do you feel better?
Do both of them feel good to you ?
So, this time you move
This feels good
It'so hot.
I feel like my stomach is going to explode...
Oh, it feels good!
I can't do it anymore.
I want to do it while looking at the sky
It'so comfortable
I can't get up.
Oh, it feels good!
It feels so good...
No way!!
No way!!!
What should we do?
We have to go home now
I couldn't hold it anymore.
It's really warm now, isn' it?
Did you feel good?
Hey, can you still do it ?
I want to try a little more.
Can we try one more time
It's just been out and it is still very hard
Don'tell your mom.
Please don' tell your mom, okay?
Your dick is so nice that I want to have a lot of sex with it
Oh no, I'm going to go.
Ugh
Ahh oh my gosh
You're also leaving?
Then next time
show me where you'll be leaving
Does it feel good
Are you ready to go?
Take a deep breath.
You're out of breath now!
Did it feel good for you today ?
If your parents aren't home, I'll tell them by the end-of month period
First thing first...
Let's take bath since we've been sweating so much
I changed my clothes, how do you like it?
Do you look good in it ?
Is this cute??
You are staring at me.
Are you still looking forward to seeing a sexy face again???
Even though we put out so many pictures just now...
...are your feelings still about being sexy?!
Because of the fact that he is really handsome!
Ah~~
He's touching his penis again
You haven't studied at all yet.
Then, look at me and tickle your belly button!
Let's feel good together
I'm going to do it alone so you can also tickle yourself
He looks very close
Let me see your face.
Show me more of your squinting face
When I look at you with a happy expression,
Sensei gets excited
Show us more
I'll give you a little bit of shiko-shiko.
The teacher went ahead...
This time, the teacher will do it for you!
I'm going to wash your face.
You were shiko-shiko properly, weren't you?
It's bigger than before!
Is it comfortable to be Shiko in hot water ?
That was good
Then let me do something more pleasant
Let my back float
Does it feel good to be licked on the belly?
I may better at being a pervert than studying.
Make your belly harder with my mouth
A lot came out
You couldn't stand it
But I'm still standing.
How do you feel?
You can't be satisfied with just one bath, right ?
Then...I'll give you more time to stand up!
There's a lot of sexual juice coming out from the tip
Are you cute now
It doesn' matter how many times
Do you want to try it?
I'll feel better.
Let's get better together!
Wow, there are so many pimples again
It felt so good
I'm glad.
Are you feeling better?
Let'study together again!
This is definitely a secret, okay?!
How do you feel now??
Show me your face!!
Why are you hiding it from us!?
Come on show us!!!
You're always writing about sex.
Did you listen to your teacher's class?
Don'tell me that you can no longer concentrate on studying because of the dizziness again
Then I'll make it clear for you
Instead,
It seems like your patience is not enough
It seems like you're not good at it, so please be patient until the teacher says yes.
Can you promise?
Then sit on the sofa and show me your penis quickly
Did you remember something erotic and were in a daze
Do I want to put it back into your pussy again
Do you think so?
You are already sexy.
Then, I'll stroke your hair with my hands
Wow!
It's getting harder and harder
Is it that good to be stroked by a teacher
Which do you like better slow or fast
Well then
Let me try slowly
You've grown up again.
I love your poop, too!
It feels so good
But you can't let it out on your own
Let's make it a little faster
Do you feel good?
Are you going to go away
No
No.
I told you, right?
You don't have enough patience
Then
Let's do it while looking at the teacher
That way you can see it closely
Ecchi
Can you stand this
It sounds ecchi
can hear
Are we going to go again
Is that so?
No.
But you were able to endure it properly, right
Then I'll count 10 again
You can add when it becomes zero
Let's go
Are you ready
Ten
Nine
Eight
Seven
Six
I've endured half of it, so
Let me show you my boobs as a reward.
You look like you're going to live
Just a little more
Great
You flew a lot.
But you were patient and great!
Did this give you some endurance?
Well, I'll do more erotic things for you because it's hard work
Stretch your legs
What are we going to be doing
I'm gonna lick your favorite nipples
I'll lick you.
You've grown up again after licking your nipples!
How about this?
You're wearing a very embarrassing outfit, aren't you
You're wearing such an embarrassing outfit, but you pooped a lot again
Then let me make your mouth feel better
Hey
Do you want the doctor to do it too?
Do you want to feel good about the teacher?
Hey, touch your boobs.
You're very good at touching it
I put a manko in my boobs
Touch your manko
So I want to kiss you again.
Hey, put your finger in the mango...
I can't do it.
It'so hard to breathe...
I'll put your kiss in it.
Wow
It's hard and big
Feels good
That part feels good
I'm scared!
He's gone already.
Sensei, it still isn't enough?
Since you're moving
can we do more of this exercise for you to see how much longer it takes
Even though he has been doing this so many times
It feels really hard
You don' feel good at all
Sensei, your gait is so comfortable.
Let's get more comfortable together!
Ah...feels good
Hey, can I do it from the back?
My back hurts because I'm in a good mood.
Hey, can you move too?
It'so hot.
I feel sick...
Uhhh
Uh
Uhh
Wow, you're making a lot of noise again
Did it feel good?
Hey
Until the last drop
Take out everything
It'still this hard
How do you feel?
Are you ready to go out with me ?
Okay, let's take a lot of rice.
Wow!
You took all the rice out for us !
Do you feel better now that we have taken so much rice out for us ?!
Ta-dah !!
This is omurice made by my teacher
It looks delicious doesn't it?!
Well then I'll start eating right away
If you don't eat a lot, you won' t be able to study.
You have no choice but bite it properly
How is it? Is delicious
He eats very deliciously
I'm happy
Eat another mouth
Eat it, Naan.
You're watching again?
Even though you were eating
Did you do something else again
I can't help it
Actually because we are eating
We shouldn' t be doing this
It's definitely just between the two of us
Maybe
Your appetite won over your desire to fight
Do you want to do something erotic with your teacher?
Well, I'll do it if we eat a little more.
Say ah!
You can't help but be patient anymore
Even though the teacher made it
Then when you feel better
When you get older, eat a lot of the food I made.
Chinchin is getting hard already
If it gets harder
The teacher will tickle you
You really love erotic things
Because we'll give you lots to tickle
Make your chin more stiff
It'so warm
Does it feel good?
I love this.
It's getting bigger and bigger!
Can i see you
What happened to your neck
You want me to lick your nipples, don't you
Because he is really erotic
Doesn'it feel good
It's getting harder and harder.
You look like you're in a bad mood again, don't you?
Can not stand it
Okay
Are you going to go out
There are so many
Maybe because I ate
But this is not enough
I want to give you a lot.
Is it hard?
Does your hand feel so good that much, teacher ?
Let me stroke more and more for you
Show us how much it feels
Are you going again
OK
Do not go
Great
It came out again.
How is it? Can you still take it out ?
What, can't you get our pants anymore
Then I'll show you my favorite one
When we see this
You want to take them off again
So
Lie down
Your really love
Sensei's panties
Wow they are hard
It's the third time.
You look like a pervert again, don't you?
Do you want to do it again ?
OK
Give me lots of hot noodles
Are you ready for that
Good
Great
This is the third time but I got most
As promised
Let us eat
Let's kiss.
I can't study at all if you do this
Because your kisses feel good,
so it makes me want to do it right away
So let us be spoiled forever
Hey
Will you lend your lips?
Show more tongue
Your lips are really soft
Want a lot of kisses
Mom and Dad are coming home tomorrow, right?
So let's have a drink before that.
I'm looking forward to how many times you can do it!
You lick your favorite nipples so much
Wow
It has become an erotic stain
Do you want me licking directly
Okay
I'll lick it for you
When your poo is hard, I'll give you a lot of shiko-shiko again.
It's getting really hard...
Sensei loves your poo!
Because it gets bigger and bigger no matter how many times
Hey
Stand up because we're going to do something more pleasant
The poops in my mouth are getting bigger an d bigger
Make is even larger
What's wrong?
You're full, aren't you.
You have a lot of hair on your face
I see
Oh yeah
Just now
This
Did you find it
Do usually use this kind
I'll use this to make you feel better.
Sit here and let me pet you a lot
Don't pet alone
If the teacher tells you,
You can always be petted
Wow
Did it go in?
Does your hand feel good too
Great sound
You're making a naughty sound.
Chinchin, Shiko-shiko
Does it feel good?
Are you going to go out of the room soon ?
It's okay! Let me pet your hand
He went out
He really went out
Did he feel good when I petted his hand
Hey
Hey, can you do it for me?
It feels good.
Come closer, please
It feels so good
It'so good.
I'm getting sleepy too...
Can you touch me?
Feels good, doesn't it!
You're doing great now
Ah, it feels good.
It feels so good!
Uh
Eh
Ehh
Uhh
No, no
It feels so good
I can'take it anymore
Give me your penis
Come here.
You like Shiko-shiko, but you also like Omanko too right?
I'll give you shikoshiku with sense's omanco
Does it feel good?
Your penis feels so good that I can't stop.
It feels so good!
Ah, it'so gross.
I'm going to go in there!
Ouch!
Your grandpa
has grown up so much
Can you make it bigger?
It tickles.
It feels so good.
Oh, no...
I'm going to puke!
It feels good
One more time
The doctor has left
So let me pat your back
Which one do you feel better?
Do you think it's going to be okay?
It is good.
You're sweating a lot
But the hand-in-hand manko felt better
I still want to do it
Hey hey
Follow me from behind
It'so hard even though I just took it out.
Ah, feels good!
It'so gross.
I'm going to tickle you with this toy
It feels good
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch.
Ouch
Which one feels better?
Massaging your eyes
or massaging your hands
Whichever feels better
Do you want to do it again?
To stroke your belly button one more time
Can I see the part of your stomach that is in pain
The part where my hands are stroking
Let's feel good together
Does it feel good
I want to do it while looking at your face.
Please tickle me a lot with your manko, Sensei!
Oh, no.
It feels so good there!
Hey...
Can you pet me more?
I want to be petted by your pussy and feel better together with you
Ah, it feels so good.
It feels so good!
I'm going to take a look at the place where you're going.
You were about go?
I'll tickle you.
Does it feel good?
Are you going to go out with me now ?
Let'see your face
You have a lot of pimples
Did that feels good for you
From now on
I'll give you a lot of kisses and pats.
Please keep it as our secret, okay?
[created using whisperjav 0.7]
In April 2017, many young people with dreams and hopes came to our Soft On Demand again this year.
So this year as well
A survey was conducted on who should be the new female employee for all male employees
As a result
Every year, the results of the survey are divided into various votes.
This year's result was very interesting that a certain female employee received many votes
So we decided to verify if the female employees who received many votes were really erotic
Excuse me
Yes
I'm sorry to call you out of the blue.
Are you okay?
Yes,I am fine
Sorry about this
It's not a bad story
Okay
This is from Yanase
You're preparing for it, right?
I'm going to record a video of the bus making.
For example Yanase-kun's girl or female employee will go there and experience AD
Like an experiment interview
If you don't mind
Would you like me do that
Yes, yes.
I'd like to confirm your will so we're filming now
Oh really?
Please let me do it
Can you do it ?
Really
Then please help us
Ok
Let's try
Thank you
But there are a lot of difficulties because this is your first time
I'm Yuto. Nice to meet you
Yes, nice to meet you
Sorry for the inconvenience
We'll send it by e-mail later
You can go back now
The plan is
Invite her on a big location
And let'see how far she can do
That's the plan.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but let me know in the comments.
The next day
Good morning!
Are you OK?
Yes
What were you doing just now
I was looking for materials of actresses to shoot
I'm looking for a job.
You have an AT company, but are you okay?
It's hard to be perfect...
But it doesn't bother me and makes my work easier
Well we can not 100%
Are you doing it now
I'm going to take a close-up of you.
We'll shoot on the same day, but don't worry about it at all
Let's do our best
Thank you
Good morning
You're in your best clothes
Yes.
I'm wearing a dress that is easy to move around in today'shoot!
It was an easy-to move dress
Is it the basic?
We'll start shooting soon, so please go inside and wait for us
Let me say hello at your room
This is my waiting room
Are you there
Good morning.
Excuse me
Good morning
I'm Hanase from SOD Production Department
Today, as AD
There are some parts that we can't do
Thank you for your cooperation
Thank you for your cooperation.
I'm going to wear AD today, so please don't bully me because it's the first year of my career as an AD actor!
Please don't be shy.
Thank you for coming today!
I was so nervous...
Let's go to the next job then
Next, let me show your room
Good luck with your sleep
Let's cheer up.
Excuse me
I'm Yanase from SOD Production Department
Today,I'll be your editor
Thank you
Are you ready?
Excuse us
How was it? Were you nervous at all.
I was very nervous, because there were so many men around me
That's right
You should say that to a man
It must be hectic for you
Yes
Because we are quite busy
Hey Sato-kun
Do you know Yanase
He is going on the show today
Oh really
Nice meeting him
I don'think so, but if you have any problems with it.
It's okay to drop it a little bit
While shooting the making of that
SOT DVD recording
This is the making
Thank you for your cooperation today
You can let me do this
Please leave
Thank you
Sorry for being busy
Follow Mr Kusawa
I'm not sure if it's true or not, but we're going to check.
We are going to do a pee-check now
Some of the people who came here today may have already peed
But there are some who haven't
So let me see if they did
You want us look at them?
Yes
This is an important job
Let's go inside.
I'll take a picture of you guys
We're going to check if there are any people who have already left the room
Would you like us help?
Over there
Yasui, this way
You can use the trash that Yuki threw away
He goes first
Please take it off.
Excuse me
Thank you
Thank you very much.
This is the last one, right?
Thank you so much!
Yes I'm fine now
So everyone's done with it
Yes, it's okay.
Everyone is ready so let us do our best for the next shoot!
Thank you very much
Let us do our best
Okay
It looks like a suit
We are in the same age group as men
So we will try to match
The girls' team it will get excited
Okay
Ready... Start
I would like to invite the actresses who participated in this time.
Good morning
How are you?
Thank you
Yes, thank you
Everyone
I'm going to have sex with you.
It's a success!
You can do anything you want here
We don't need any rubber bands
Sex is over!
I want to have more sex.
Me too, but...
Sex is over!!
This one's Pepe'so let me do it for you
Here we go
Oh yeah
Can you see?
Really
But this isn't good
It looks like a firework
Thank you.
Thank you very much!
How was it?
It's amazing...
I felt like a real person
This is my first time to see the live performance
You should speak more
Speak more!?
There's a tissue here, and the trash is over there.
Let me hear your voice more clearly!
Oh that was good
Next preparation
The next day
Good work today
What are you doing?
Organizing equipment
We only have one girl
So, I'm going to do AD work this time.
It's also a report...
What is the meaning of AD work?
When you come here for hot springs
You have no choice but understand actresses' feelings
Is that so
For example
Let me say stand-in
When they say what kind
We have an explanation
At that time
I'll do it with you, or at the house like a little while ago
It's parallel to something like checking
Because there are also actors who don't stand up
Or care for such things
So that kind of business will come out from this time
Do you hear it somehow?
Yes!
Well then
There is definitely something embarrassing
I think so, but it's a job.
Let me do my best and let you go
Then everyone can get the trust of girls
Everyone will rely on you
Yes!
If there is anything else
Please call
Do your best
It is hot
Good morning
It'so hot.
Thank you very much!
Natsume-san?
Thank you very much
Yes, it is OK
Here we go
What should I do!?
Otsuki san
What does this mean?!
This is a big problem
It's like this.
If you want to take part in the bus tour, you have go over the bridge first!
What did she say?
As I said before if you want take part in a bus tour
Go over that bridge
You can do it by yourself
Jump off
Human horse
Thanking
Good job
Yayyyy!
Wait a minute.
Thank you very much
I wonder if it's here...
It was not there
Yes, please give me space
It is in the real center mode
Oh yes
Thank you
We're going to play a game now.
Please look at the board, everyone!
Game
Yaya-san will do it for us in Mogi
Can you show your dick?
Sorry
Let's go one by one
It is our job
Good luck!
Please shake your body.
Shake, shake...
With both hands
Hurry up because we're in the middle of a shoot
Now you'll be shaking
I don't know how it will turn out but
I think you're going to lose.
If you want, we won't let you go in one by one
Why?
Because if he goes in there's no way out
So when it comes down on him
He has a chance of getting away
But once this guy leaves
You can still win
It means that the chances are high
Yes
I see.
Did you revive?
Yes, yes
Can we take a picture with you guys
Please
Thank you
It'so good
How is it
Good
So good
I'm not sure if it's going to work.
It won't come out because we're doing a live broadcast, right?
We haven' noticed yet...
Excuse me!
The real thing is about to start so please move back together with us for now
Game ready
Start
I'm going to eat it.
Cut!
Can we move on to the next scene?
Please lie down here, three of you
Next is a game where they have to chew oranges fast
Where's Erii-san
Coming back
I'll eat it.
Please wait a moment, we will press the button
Which team can eat more mandarin?
The woman should put the mandarin in her mouth
This man wants to have some mandarins
Do you want some mandarins!
Let me have them
Let me eat it!
Let him have a bite of the orange.
He'still eating it?
Orange, orange...
Orange-orange
I want to give you some
Give us some
Delicious
Wait
That was what we did
The next game is...
Who can eat a lot of mandarin oranges?
Game start!
White, red.
Red
Chance
Zero
Please!
Go, go.
I think we can win this game
Pink team seems to be strong
Pink team is really strong
Let's announce the result
From 4th place
The fourth place goes to
Let's taste it!
Okay, cut.
Can I eat this?
Go ahead and eat as much you want to
Lastly
If we can endure the amazing technique of an AV actress
We will be able live
Please go for it
Girls, please show us your Sugoteku.
Let me see your Sugoteku!
I don't have a Sugoteko so...
You do have one though?
No
Yes
Ready set go
This is the last game
It's me!
If you can bear with the amazing technique of an AV actress,
it is a live friendship.
Ready? Start
I will not give it to you immediately because there are many people who have come
Here is the pose of Harlem.
Ready, go!
This is the play of Harlem by winning team!!
The game will be over now
It's time for Harlems
I'm Chiba
That's a bad way to say it
You got 70 points
Please sit on the chair
You can go back
Pants and glasses
A few minutes later
Ready, go!
Konnichiwa.
Do you want to take a bath?
Yes we do!!
You're all sweaty now...
But there are two types of hot water for men and women in the bathroom
One is hell and the other one is heaven
It's called a bath.
Please choose which one you want to take!
I've decided on the place for you guys
Which way?
Let' go right away
3,2
What?
I'm in heaven.
There's nothing here, right...
Yeah!
Poor guys
Men don't get along with each other
Are you guys coming?!
I wanna do it so bad
We've only done it once
Do you have any particular thing to show us
Or just a little bit of sexiness
Sexines-
You want me out
Just now
Well
But I want to do it, because you did it with a hand-held machine earlier.
If that happens...
Can't you take off your clothes?
You poor thing
Poor thing
There's only one person left
It won' t be more than 9 years old
Please
Please do.
I'm glad that you are here with us today,
because we can't leave you alone
or a beautiful actress like her behind
What kind of friendship story is this?
It's good!
It's a good story.
So,
You are Yuta-san
I'll give you the job
Is it OK?
Even for me
Is it really okay to do this
Let three of us
But there is one condition
Because we are employees
We have an interview
Can
Of course
I can't do it.
Let's do it with three people
Please
It is a woman
Thank you
You look like the story of good men
There are many guys
Do you like that?
Then, take off your microphone
Take off the microphone
Really
Are you sure?
If you lie to me, I'll be angry.
Here is my bag!
You can keep it here
She's lying
Can we help her take off the clothes
Excuse us
Start
Lift up
I'm not used to it yet.
You want to put this on, right?
Can we take a picture of you wearing that one time
Didn't she say something about being sexy
There are people who are sexy
It's a bit erotic.
Isn't it?
Yuzawa-san, you are so funny!
You made me sad...
He came back to us
He is poor
Don' do that
This pipe is very beautiful
Very beautiful
There are so many types of bread.
It's like this...
It is really beautiful!
Can I eat it?
What kind do you like the most ?
Soy sauce
Do you see it??
I was able to do it.
Thank you very much
You gave me a free service
I did
2,000 yen
It was so good.
I didn't know that you are such a great actor, Erii-san!
Thank you for your cooperation next time as well
Give me the money!!
OK
Please say something to the camera
That's it
Pass this over
Interview...
Please give us an interview
I'm going to do it.
You've been doing this for a while, haven't you?
Thank you for your hard work!
How should we react when they see us like this...
We did it without thinking much of the situation
Has the meeting started yet?!
Yes
It's open
Really!?
Oh really!!
Are there any questions left??
There are still some
I'm going to work now.
Thank you for your hard work!
She is working so hard!!
Aren't you tired?
No, thank you very much
You were taking a rest
We had sex over there
What!?
Good job
Let's watch the interview and do our work
Yes
I'm not good at English.
Are you okay?
The room behind is very expensive, but...
You're naked!
It's Yoripi-dori.
This is embarrassing
Does it suit me well
It suits you
Let's go to the actual shooting.
Ready, start!
Let me see a girl first
I'm not ready yet
She is about that old lady
Please ask her
This is my first time
Really?
Ask the girl directly
Do it
I'm waiting for you to do it.
You should look at the audience more
Because your eyes are out of focus now
Brother!
Come here
Look at him
He is kind
Brother, he is kind
There are a lot of people.
Let's go to the next one!
Are you ready?
Yes, let' s go
Do we have enough tickets for this time too!?
We only have 20 thousand yen
OK
I'm ready
Which one do you want me take with us
Which is it
You mean which way
This way
This
How about this girl
That girl
Is that okay
Sure
She said yes
Yay
Really
It's okay.
I have more money than you do, though...
What are you talking about?
You've got a lot of money now!
This is the only way to win this game
She has 50%
I happen to have a room that my aunt used.
Let's go together!
Go with me, please
Please
Go with her
Thank you
Excuse us
Did you enjoy?
Thanks
She is waiting for the staff
I'm waiting for you to sign it.
Please go inside the room and take a look at her.
Please come inside the room and take care of me, please
Close your back
You have no face
I'll be right there.
Thank you very much!
Nice to meet you, too
Me too
Sorry that we are not actresses
No problem
This one is better
It's good
I'm happy. Thank you very much
Are you inexperienced?
No, not at all
Have you ever seen a shy girl before
Yes
You are
Do you like it?
I've been curious about this since the morning.
You're like an old lady, right now
Sorry for being weird
The eyes are in a good place
Would you touch it
It's perfect
I think that's what they're aiming for.
They can attack you while saying,
crush your eyes!
It looks like Osaka too
You can do whatever you want
Your skin is so beautiful
Mine is also a bit pale
Really
White and beautiful
It's good to be wearing a mask, isn't it?
Well...I'm embarrassed now because of my job and doing something bad at the same time
Kato Momoka-san
Yes
Satou-san
She is working in this company
Right
Excuse me
Okay.
I'm getting excited!
To think that it's me in the picture...
It really is very white, isn't it?
Your lips are soft and pleasant to look at
That makes me happy
I'm so happy.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good to you ?
That makes me happy
Please make me more comfortable
Yes
Please make my feeling better
Really
Oh yes
Your penis is very thin
I'm going to lick you.
You can also lick my chinchin
It feels good
Does it feel good?
What do you like being done
I want a lot of food
A lot
Oh, it's hot.
It feels good!
It goes all the way to here...
Please hold on tight
You can laugh now
Isn'this hard?
It feels good.
I'll put it on you now
You feel a lot of things, and that makes me happy
Do you like cleaning?
Yes
Let's put this in
What's going on?
Here.
Where are you hitting now ?
I'm hitting there!
My buttocks...
Really, it hurts so much
But it feels good
I'm so happy.
It's hot!
It was just a little bit...
Thank you very much
Thank you
I'm going to take off the rubber band.
Does it hurt?
It's okay
Can you let me go out of your arms, please
Thank you
Thank you so much
You're welcome
That was a healing sex
I'm glad you felt that way.
How did you feel?
It was very pleasant
Did it hurt on the way there or not at all
No, it didn't
Isn' t is tight
Thank you so much
Thank you for your hard work.
Which one do you like, Ame-chan?
I'll take the purple one
I'm so happy
Is it sweet
Thank you very much today
See him off
Please enjoy yourself again
Thanks
Thank you very much. I'll come back again
Thank you
It was really good
How do you feel?
Do we go to the next one
Let'see
But there may be no more
Thanks
Please tell me
Is this place okay?
It's open now.
I'm coming in!
The next customer is here, so let me give you a service right away
Thank you
Can we buy half and half of the food
You can go now.
The customers are waiting for you, so please hurry up and come in!
I'm wearing a rubber band around my neck but it's okay?
Please
Are you okay with this?
Okay
We'll clean your ears when the bath is over
Which part do you like best
This one
Yeah
There.
Can I let it go?
Go ahead
It's big
What do you like to be done
Do you like being licked
Does it feel good here
Here
Feels good
Is this
How is it?
Your gums are hard.
It'so big!
Can I put this in your mouth now, please
Let me apply some ointment
What kind of posture do you like the most
The best one
Me too
I'm going to clean your ears.
Okay, let'start cleaning your ears!
Please put the cotton swab in my ear
Put it in
Yes
Does this hurt?
It hurts
It's very narrow.
I'm so tired...
What is it?
Do you want some water, too...?
My stomach hurts!
Please give me a lot of water...!
Oh my gosh!!
Wow!
Thank you.
It's amazing
Can I touch your feet?
Please hold on
Sorry, it was a little early
Excuse me
Let's change your clothes
It doesn't hurt, does it?
Thank you so much
How was the surgery today
It went well
Me too
I'm glad you're okay.
Isn't it tight?
Thank you for your hard work today!
Oh, thank God...
It's raining a lot
Thank you very much
Please enjoy yourself
Thanks
Good morning.
Thank you for your hard work today!
I'm sorry to wake you up before going back home, because we have a lot of work tomorrow as well
How was it working with AD?
It was harder than what imagined
We didn't know how and where should move
And there were so many people
This is the second time I've done it.
The actress was amazing!
She overpowered me and made me cry
But,I'll do my best
Yes
More than today
Please prepare for tomorrow
Thank you
Good night
Good night.
The next day
I'm going to do my best.
That's what we're doing now, right?
Thanks to you guys!
What is the name of this dance in the play?
Panko
Here it goes
Ready, action!
Let'start the Dynamico.
There are people crying over there
If you don't stand up for shooting
Can I help you?
With my hand
You cry because it doesn' turn into a work
It is your job to do that
Let's help her.
I was told not to participate in this game, but...
Touch me!
It is OK to take it out?
How do you feel?
Do you feel good now ?
I'm feeling great.
Don't you have any pain in your body anymore
No, it's fine
I'm looking forward to it.
Do your best alone!
There are a lot of guys, so you can't have fun with all the users?
Girls will never be enough for sure
Can you mix in some more girls
What do you mean by that
I don't know, so it's not good to stop the user and go home.
It is a last scene after all
So you can take off your skin here
That is also as work
You are happy with that
The user will be happy
Then give this
Can you hold thiis?
Go where the overflowing man
Let's go to the man and say, I'll help you.
Where are you going?
The person just now is out of breath so let him come here
Good luck
Okay let' get in
Do you see anyone waiting for the guy
There he is
Sit down.
Are you enjoying?
I went away immediately
Did you go away immediately
Let's enjoy again
We have time until the end
It doesn't hurt
This is the last one.
Thank you very much!
It'so heavy!!
I want to take revenge on him...
Oh, he came back!!!
Why are you laughing?
Do you want a revenge on me??
No way....
It'so hot!
Do you want to join?
Can I join in the video too??
I want touch it.
How is it?
Please!
It'so good!
I'm getting bigger.
You are bigger than before, aren't you?
It feels good
Yes
Can we go down again
Sure
Wow
Feels great
Sorry, what did you say?
It feels so good!!
Oh my god...
Feels great!!!
It feels so good.
I feel so good!
Does it feel good?
Baby, you are going to die!!
I feel so good.
It feels so good!
Oppa, it feels great
Let'stay here
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
It'so hot!
How do you feel now ?
Inside...
Thank you very much !
It'so big!
I got it.
You got two of them at once?
Yes, that was great
It gets bigger as you put in more
Please hold this
Take this!
It feels good.
Please put it in again
I want more
Do you feel good?
Yes, it's great!
It is very hard...
Oh, it hurts.
It's gone again...
I'm glad you're feeling better now!
You've got a lot of blood on your face
He might bite the window
Who is that?
What is this?!
It'so hot.
How do you feel?
I'm feeling great!
Can we put it in your mouth now!?
It feels good, doesn't it?!
Just one more time.
Is that so?
Yanase-chan, it's over!
It is over...
What are you complaining about?!
I'm not done yet...!
You're not done yeet!! We have to clean up afterwards!!!
Don't look so dissatisfied.
Clean up the mess, quickly!
You don' t have to look so displeased
Thank you very much
Let's go
Thanks
Satsuki, come here.
Did you turn on the switch?
I was having fun at last but it's over now...
So that makes me want to have more fun by myself!
It is a rule after all
The next day
Let's do it in pairs! 6-2,6
We're going up
Everyone did you have fun?
Good job
Thank you for your hard work.
You were the last one to go through a rough time, how was it?
There are so many people like this in the crowd and I felt really embarrassed
It was my first time but
Even though were nervous
I was happy, but at the end it made me want him to feel better.
You looked like you wanted to be in a good mood and that's not what happened?
No no! It was just my wish for him
Because he is an employee
Yes because of that
So from now on too
We will do our best
I'll do my best.
This is the end of today'shooting, so thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much
Good luck with your training
Thank you
Thank You
It is over
Thank you.
[created using whisperjav 0.7]